Guide to the Seattle Department of Parks and Recreation Planning, Construction and Maintenance Records 1928-1994
Seattle Municipal Archives
Planning, Construction and Maintenance Records
1928-1994
1950-1992
Seattle Municipal Archives PO Box 94728 600 Fourth Avenue, Floor 3 Seattle, WA 98124-4728 Phone: 206/233-7807 Email: archives@seattle.gov http://www.seattle.gov/cityarchives
5804-05
Seattle (Wash.). Dept. of Parks and Recreation. Facilities Maintenance Division
67.62 cubic ft. 68 boxes; 16 reels of microfilm
Records of the Parks Department's Facilities Maintenance Division. The records document changes and improvements in Seattle parks as well as the planning, design, and construction of new parks.
Historical Note
The Department of Parks and Recreation maintains the City's parks, shorelines, and boulevards; and administers community centers, public golf courses, and other athletic and cultural facilities. Seattle's first park was established in 1884 after David Denny donated land to the City for that purpose. At that time, a three-member park committee, with limited authority, was created to manage the nascent park system. A Board of Parks Commissioners was established in 1890 with control over all public parks and authority to appoint a Parks Superintendent. In 1896, the City Charter created the position of Superintendent of Streets, Sewers and Parks. The Parks Department became a separate entity in 1904. In 1926, a City Charter amendment abolished the position of Superintendent, distributing its responsibilities between the Head Gardener and the Landscape Architect. A 1948 City Charter amendment required the Board of Park Commissioners to appoint a park superintendent to administer the department. In 1967, another City Charter Amendment reconstituted the Board as an advisory body to the Mayor and City Council, changed the agency name to Department of Parks and Recreation, and placed fiscal and operational administration under the superintendent. In 1902 the City hired the Olmsted Brothers, the country's premier landscape architectural firm, to design a parks and boulevards system. Although not all of the plan was implemented, the Olmsted legacy is evident in many of Seattle's parks and boulevards. The City acquired significant amounts of property for park purposes following the turn of the 20th Century, but in 1926 further acquisition was limited by a City Charter amendment that stipulated only money in the Park Fund could be used for that purpose. However, in the 1970s the Forward Thrust Bond issue, along with federal grants and the Seattle Model City Program, supported the largest expansion of the Park system in Seattle history. These programs funded more than 70 new parks and park facilities. The Department manages over 6,000 acres of park land, over two dozen community centers, five municipal golf courses, the Aquarium, and many other recreational and athletic facilities.
This series documents changes and improvements in Seattle parks, as well as the construction of new parks, through the records of the Facilities Maintenance Division. These activities were funded through Forward Thrust, Model City Program, and other agencies, as well as with Parks Department monies. The planning, design, and construction phases of projects are documented. Records are primarily those of project coordinators, as well as engineers, the city architect, and the Parks Superintendent.
The record series contains correspondence, contracts and agreements, reports, maps, drawings, newspaper clippings, and photographs. The series offers good snapshots of neighborhood character because community input was often an important part of the process of improving or developing new parks. The relationship between the Parks Department and contractors is also very well documented, especially through correspondence and meeting minutes which document projects through various stages. When more than one department or entity outside of the City are involved, as in the construction of the Aquarium or Freeway Park, for example, interdepartmental relationships are well documented through memoranda, reports and contracts.
Many projects in the collection are of note. One is the documentation of the Burke-Gilman Trail, which covers the years 1973 to 1980 and includes material on the land transfer between the railroad and the City, as well as correspondence between City departments and with community groups. The Capitol Hill Viewpoint or Louis Boren Lookout was designed by Victor Steinbrueck and his correspondence with the City is included in the project files.
The Discovery Park project is especially well documented. Land transfer, community input, construction, and the relationship between the City and the United Indians of All Tribes, as well as other issues relating to the development of the park, are documented in the records. The records include correspondence with Bernie Whitebear and documentation of various court proceedings with Margaret Coughlin.
Also well represented is the Thornton Creek area, especially the environmental studies done surrounding the idea of an urban park and trail. Additionally, the planning efforts and studies relating to the central waterfront area, as well, including explorations of a marina and convention center are detailed in the records. The large volume of records related to Magnuson Park reflect the complex decision-making process regarding its use.
In some cases, information can be found in more than one place in the series. Mini-parks are listed under the name of the specific park, but there are also folders under "small parks and recreation areas" which have information on mini-parks. Some park plans, such as South Lake Union Park, were explored, but not executed.
Arranged into four subseries: Project files, Planning files, Design/Architect's files and Microfilmed drawings.
Records are open to the public.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Whitebear, Bernie; Coughlin, Margaret, 1912-1996--Trials, litigation, etc.; Steinbrueck, Victor; Jessel, Jim; Brown, Buddy; Ferrero, Ernie; Vibber, John Russell, 1915-
Seattle (Wash.). Dept. of Parks and Recreation. Facilities Maintenance Division; Seattle (Wash.). Dept. of Parks and Recreation; United Indians of All Tribes Foundation; Seattle Aquarium; University of Washington. Arboretum
Seattle (Wash.); Burke Gilman Trail (Wash.); Discovery Park (Seattle, Wash.); Fort Lawton (Seattle, Wash.); Freeway Park (Seattle, Wash.); Gas Works Park (Seattle, Wash.); Louisa Boren Lookout (Seattle, Wash.); Occidental Park (Seattle, Wash.); Warren G. Magnuson Park (Seattle, Wash.); Westlake Park (Seattle, Wash.); Woodland Park Zoo
Parks--Washington (State)--Seattle; Playgrounds--Washington (State)--Seattle; Public art--Washington (State)--Seattle; Community centers--Washington (State)--Seattle; Swimming pools--Washington (State)--Seattle; Recreation areas and people with disabilities--Washington (State)--Seattle; Sports facilities--Washington (State)--Seattle; Sports facilities--Lighting--Washington (State)--Seattle; Urban parks--Washington (State)--Seattle; Playgrounds--Equipment and supplies--Washington (State)--Seattle; Reservoirs--Design and construction--Washington (State)--Seattle; Golf courses--Washington (State)--Seattle
Parks and Playgrounds; Seattle; Sports and Recreation; Photographs
Photographs; Design Drawings; Maps; Correspondence; Memorandums; Contracts; Reports; Drawings; Photographic prints; Negatives; Clippings; Microfilms
The following section contains a detailed listing of the materials in the collection.
- Project files, 1928-1994
  - Alki Avenue: Master Plan, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Alki Avenue Master Plan, 1974 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Alki Avenue: Improvements General, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Alki Avenue: Improvements - Project Description, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Alki Avenue: Improvements - Planning and Program, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Alki Avenue: Improvements - Planning and Program, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Alki Avenue: Improvements - Financial, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Alki Avenue: Improvements - Contracts and Agreements, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 1/8)
  - Alki Project, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Alki Avenue: Newspaper Clippings, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Alki Avenue: Maps, undated (Box-folder 1/11)
  - Alki Playground Tennis Courts: High pressure sodium vapor lighting, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 1/12)
  - All Weather Playfield Study, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 1/13)
  - Aquarium: Freshwater Conversion, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 1/14)
  - Aquarium: Shoreline Permits, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 1/15)
  - Aquarium: Shoreline Permits, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 1/16)
  - Aquarium: Marine Mammal Barriers, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 1/17)
  - Aquarium: Corrosion Study - Galka Associates, 1979 (Box-folder 1/18)
  - Aquarium: General - Parking, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 1/19)
  - Aquarium: Parking, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 1/20)
  - Aquarium: Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 1/21)
  - Aquarium: Project Manager's Notebook, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 1/22)
  - Aquarium: Site Selection, 1971 (Box-folder 1/23)
  - Aquarium: Environmental Impact Statement, 1974 (Box-folder 1/24)
  - Aquarium: Bicentennial Event, 1976 (Box-folder 1/25)
  - Aquarium: Piers 60 61, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 1/26)
  - Aquarium: Economic Study, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 1/27)
  - Aquarium: Acoustic Study, 1974 (Box-folder 1/28)
  - Aquarium: Contracts and Agreements, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 1/29)
  - Aquarium: Financial, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 1/30)
  - Aquarium: Planning and Program, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 1/31)
  - Aquarium: Planning and Program, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 1/32)
  - Aquarium: Project Description, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 1/33)
  - Aquarium: Newspaper Clippings, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 1/34)
  - Aquarium - Tropical Pacific Exhibit Correspondence June - Dec., 1979 (Box-folder 1/35)
  - Aquarium - Tropical Pacific Exhibit, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 1/36)
  - Aquarium: Tropical Pacific Exhibit - Project File Jan - April, 1980 (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Aquarium: Tropical Pacific Exhibit - Project File May - June, 1980 (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Aquarium: Tropical Pacific Exhibit: Project File - July, 1980 (Box-folder 2/3)
  - Aquarium: Tropical Pacific Exhibit August - December, 1980 (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Aquarium: Tropical Pacific Exhibit Jan - March, 1981 (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Aquarium Tropical Pacific Exhibit Project File April - May, 1981 (Box-folder 2/6)
  - Aquarium: Tropical Pacific Exhibit Project Files June - July, 1981 (Box-folder 2/7)
  - Aquarium: Tropical Pacific Exhibit Project File Aug. - Dec., 1981 (Box-folder 2/8)
  - Aquarium: Tropical Pacific Exhibit Project File Jan. - May, 1982 (Box-folder 2/9)
  - Aquarium: Tropical Pacific Exhibit Project File June - Dec, 1982 (Box-folder 2/10)
  - Aquarium: Tropical Pacific Exhibit - Project File, 1983 (Box-folder 2/11)
  - Aquarium: Tropical Pacific Exhibit Project File Jan. - July, 1984 (Box-folder 2/12)
  - Aquarium: Tropical Pacific Exhibit Project File July - December, 1984 (Box-folder 2/13)
  - Aquarium: Tropical Pacific Exhibit Project File - January, 1985 (Box-folder 2/14)
  - Aquarium: Tropical Pacific Exhibit Newspaper Clippings, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 2/15)
  - Arboretum Bike Path Project File, 1971-1982 (Box-folder 2/16)
  - Arboretum Bikeway: Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 2/17)
  - Arboretum: Lighting, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 2/18)
  - Arboretum: Management / University of Washington, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 2/19)
  - Arboretum: Management / University of Washington, 1973 (Box-folder 2/20)
  - Arboretum: Management / University of Washington Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 2/21)
  - Arboretum: Visitor's Center Project File, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 2/22)
  - Arboretum: Visitor's Center Project File Jan. - July, 1982 (Box-folder 2/23)
  - Arboretum: Visitors Center Project File August - December, 1982 (Box-folder 2/24)
  - Arboretum: Visitor's Center Project File Jan. - April, 1983 (Box-folder 2/25)
  - Arboretum: Visitor's Center Project File May - June, 1983 (Box-folder 2/26)
  - Arboretum: Visitor's Center Project File July - October, 1983 (Box-folder 3/1)
  - Arboretum: Visitor's Center Project File November - December, 1983 (Box-folder 3/2)
  - Arboretum: Visitor's Center Project File Jan - June, 1984 (Box-folder 3/3)
  - Arboretum: Visitor's Center and Site Improvement July - Dec., 1984 (Box-folder 3/4)
  - Arboretum: Visitor's Center Project File Jan - June, 1985 (Box-folder 3/5)
  - Arboretum: Visitor's Center Project File July - Dec., 1985 (Box-folder 3/6)
  - Arboretum: Visitor's Center Project File Jan - June, 1986 (Box-folder 3/7)
  - Arboretum: Visitor's Center Project File July - Dec., 1986 (Box-folder 3/8)
  - Arboretum: Visitor's Center Project File, 1987 (Box-folder 3/9)
  - Arboretum: Visitor's Center Lawsuit Parks Construction v. The Arboretum Foundation et. al., 1988-1990 (Box-folder 3/10)
  - Arboretum Visitor's Center: Lawsuit - Deposition of E. Ferrero, 1990 (Box-folder 3/11)
  - Arboretum: Visitor's Center Contract Amendments, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 3/12)
  - Arboretum: Visitor's Center Newspaper Clippings, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 3/13)
  - Don Armeni Park: Parlato Bench Donation, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 3/14)
  - Don Armeni Park: Boat Launching Ramp, 1973-1984 (Box-folder 3/15)
  - Don Armeni Park: Design Selection, 1981 (Box-folder 3/16)
  - Don Armeni Park: Design Contract, 1981 (Box-folder 3/17)
  - Don Armeni Park: Dedication, 1983 (Box-folder 3/18)
  - Don Armeni Park: Photographs, 1969-1983 (Box-folder 3/19)
  - Don Armeni Park: Preconstruction Meeting and Reports, 1982 (Box-folder 3/20)
  - Don Armeni Park: Budget, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 3/21)
  - Don Armeni Park: Program, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 3/22)
  - Don Armeni: Program, 1980 (Box-folder 3/23)
  - Don Armeni Park: Program, 1981 (Box-folder 3/24)
  - Don Armeni Park: Program Files, 1982 (Box-folder 3/25)
  - Don Armeni Project Files, 1983 (Box-folder 3/26)
  - Don Armeni Program File, 1984 (Box-folder 3/27)
  - Don Armeni Park: Shoreline Development Permit, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 3/28)
  - Don Armeni Park: Trees, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 3/29)
  - Don Armeni Park: Trees, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 3/30)
  - Don Armeni Park: Boat Launching, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 4/1)
  - Don Armeni Park: Newspaper Clippings, 1973-1983 (Box-folder 4/2)
  - Armory Park, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 4/3)
  - Atlantic City Boat Ramp Project File, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 4/4)
  - Atlantic City Boat Ramp Project File January - June, 1972 (Box-folder 4/5)
  - Atlantic City Boat Ramp Project File: July - December, 1972 (Box-folder 4/6)
  - Atlantic City Boat Ramp Project File, 1973 (Box-folder 4/7)
  - Atlantic City Boat Ramp Project File, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 4/8)
  - Atlantic City Boat Ramp: Shoreline Management Act Permit, 1972 (Box-folder 4/9)
  - Atlantic City Boat Ramp: Maps Drawings (Box-folder 4/10)
  - Atlantic City Boat Ramp: Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 4/11)
  - Atlantic City Park Extension, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 4/12)
  - Ballard Recreation Center / Playground (includes maps drawing), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 4/13)
  - Ballard Recreation Center: Lighting, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 4/14)
  - Ballard Swimming Pool: Project File, 1968 (Box-folder 4/15)
  - Ballard Swimming Pool: Project File, 1969 (Box-folder 4/16)
  - Ballard Swimming Pool: Project File, 1970 (Box-folder 4/17)
  - Ballard Swimming Pool: Project File, 1971 (Box-folder 4/18)
  - Ballard Swimming Pool: Project File, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 4/19)
  - Ballard Pool: Newspaper Clippings, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 4/20)
  - Ballard Swimming Pool Roof, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 4/21)
  - Ballard Tennis Courts, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 4/22)
  - Ballard Tennis Courts, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 4/23)
  - Bergen Place (Ballard Circle Park), 1974 (Box-folder 4/24)
  - Bergen Place (Ballard Circle Park), 1975 (Box-folder 4/25)
  - Bergen Place (Ballard Circle Park), 1976-1977 (Box-folder 4/26)
  - Bergen Place (Ballard Circle Park) Newspaper Clippings, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 4/27)
  - Banner Place Viewpoint, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 5/1)
  - Bar - S Playground, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 5/2)
  - Powell Barnett Playground (Empire Way Playground), 1974 (Box-folder 5/3)
  - Bathhouse Renovation, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 5/4)
  - Bathhouse Renovation: Newspaper Clippings, 1971 (Box-folder 5/5)
  - Beacon Hill Playground, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 5/6)
  - Beacon Hill Playground, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 5/7)
  - Beer Sheva Park / Atlantic City Park, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 5/8)
  - Beer Sheva / Atlantic City Park: Newspaper Clippings, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 5/9)
  - Benefit Playground, 1978 (Box-folder 5/10)
  - Benefit Playground, 1979 (Box-folder 5/11)
  - Benefit Playground Project File January - July, 1980 (Box-folder 5/12)
  - Benefit Playground Project File August - December, 1980 (Box-folder 5/13)
  - Benefit Playground, 1981 (Box-folder 5/14)
  - Benefit Playground (includes Photographs), 1981-1982 (Box-folder 5/15)
  - Bradner Place Park, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 5/16)
  - Bradner Playfield Comfort Station, 1979 (Box-folder 5/17)
  - Brighton Playfield Shelterhouse Rehabilitation, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 5/18)
  - Brighton Neighborhood Playground, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 5/19)
  - Broadway Playfield / Lincoln Reservoir: Project Files Reservoir Cover, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 5/20)
  - Broadway Playfield / Lincoln Park: Reservoir Cover Consultant Interviews and Landscape Design Agreement, 1972 (Box-folder 5/21)
  - Broadway Playfield / Lincoln Reservoir: Reservoir Cover, 1973 (Box-folder 5/22)
  - Broadway Playfield / Reservoir Cover Project Files, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 5/23)
  - Broadway Playfield / Lincoln Reservoir: Playfield Rehabilitation, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5/24)
  - Broadway Playfield Lincoln Reservoir - Reservoir Cover Financial / Funding, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 5/25)
  - Broadway Playfield Lincoln Reservoir: Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 5/26)
  - Broadway Playfield / Lincoln Reservoir Planning Program, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 5/27)
  - Broadway Playfield / Lincoln Reservoir Planning Program, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 5/28)
  - Broadway Playfield / Lincoln Reservoir Photographs Maps ( prints slides), 1971 (Box-folder 5/29)
  - Broadway Playfield Lincoln Reservoir: Newspaper Clippings, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 5/30)
  - Bryant Neighborhood Playground: Proposal, Acquisition Project Description, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 6/1)
  - Bryant Neighborhood Playground, 1975 (Box-folder 6/2)
  - Bryant Neighborhood Playground: Project File Jan. - June, 1976 (Box-folder 6/3)
  - Bryant Neighborhood Playground July - Dec., 1976 (Box-folder 6/4)
  - Bryant Neighborhood Playground Petitions, 1975 (Box-folder 6/5)
  - Bryant Neighborhood Playground: Project File, 1977 (Box-folder 6/6)
  - Bryant Neighborhood Playground: Project File, 1978 (Box-folder 6/7)
  - Bryant Neighborhood Playground: Drawings by School Children, 1977 (Box-folder 6/8)
  - Bryant Neighborhood Playground: Drawings by School Children, 1977 (Box-folder 6/9)
  - Bryant Neighborhood Playground: Newspaper Clippings, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 6/10)
  - Burke Gilman Place Park, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 6/11)
  - Burke Gilman Place Park, 1984 (Box-folder 6/12)
  - Burke - Gilman Place Park: Demolition of Radio Transmitter Building., 1983-1984 (Box-folder 6/13)
  - Burke Gilman Trail: History, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 6/14)
  - Burke Gilman Trail: Maps, undated (Box-folder 6/15)
  - Burke Gilman Trail: Burlington Northern Right - of - Way Acquisition, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 6/16)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Burlington Northern Right - of - Way, 1973 (Box-folder 6/17)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Acquisition of Burlington Northern Right - of - Way, 1974 (Box-folder 6/18)
  - Burke Gilman Trail: Burlington Northern Property, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 6/19)
  - Burke Gilman Trail: Sand Point Surplus Property, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 6/20)
  - Burke Gilman Trail: Planning, 1975 (Box-folder 6/21)
  - Burke Gilman Trail: Phase I Specifications, 1976 (Box-folder 6/22)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Phase I Budget, 1976 (Box-folder 6/23)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Phase I Construction, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 6/24)
  - Burke Gilman Trail: Design Contract, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 6/25)
  - Burke Gilman Trail: Design Commission, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 6/26)
  - Burke Gilman Trail: Engineering Dept., 1974-1975 (Box-folder 6/27)
  - Burke Gilman Trail: Engineering, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 6/28)
  - Burke Gilman Trail: Planned Unit Development (PUD), 1976-1977 (Box-folder 7/1)
  - Burke Gilman Trail: Shoreline Management Permit, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 7/2)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Fine Police Review, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 7/3)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Federal Aid Urban System Funds, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 7/4)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Maintenance, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 7/5)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Phase 2 Construction, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 7/6)
  - Burke Gilman Trail Construction Phase II Eng. Dept. Contract, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 7/7)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Design Contract, 1976 (Box-folder 7/8)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Phase II - Financial, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 7/9)
  - Burke Gilman Trail: Metro Council Water Quality, 1975 (Box-folder 7/10)
  - Burke Gilman Trail: Public Meetings Input, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 7/11)
  - Burke Gilman Trail: Public Meetings March 29, 1976 (Box-folder 7/12)
  - Burke Gilman Trail: Permits, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 7/13)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: State Federal Documents, 1977 (Box-folder 7/14)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Citizen Committees, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 7/15)
  - Burke Gilman Trail: Noise Environmental Impact Statement, 1974 (Box-folder 7/16)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Environmental Impact Statement, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 7/17)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Lake Forest Park WA State IAC on Recreation Application, 1977 (Box-folder 7/18)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: U of W Plant Engineering Office, 1974 (Box-folder 7/19)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Surfacing, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 7/20)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Anton Hiksen, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 7/21)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Martin E. Claspill Case, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 7/22)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Surveys, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 7/23)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Property Management D.N.R., 1975-1977 (Box-folder 7/24)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Property Exchange, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 7/25)
  - Burke - Gilman: Property / Right - of - Way, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 7/26)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Sand Point Surplus Property, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 7/27)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Citizen Letters, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 7/28)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Project File, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 7/29)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Project File, 1976 (Box-folder 7/30)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Project File Aug. - Dec., 1977 (Box-folder 7/31)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Project File, 1978 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Project File, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail: Newspaper Clippings, 1974-1985 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Camp O.O. Denny Project File, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Fort Lawton An / FSC-1 Tactical Facilities AAOC Main Building, architectural drawings; 21 sheets F-8-4-2, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Fort Lawton ADC Operations Building JMDC architectural drawings; 11 sheets F-8-4-1, 1959 (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Camp O.O. Denny Project File, 1970 (Box-folder 8/5)
  - Camp O.O. Denny, 1971 (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Camp O.O. Denny Project File, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 8/7)
  - Camp O.O. Denny Project File, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Camp O.O. Denny Project File, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 8/9)
  - Camp O.O. Denny Project File, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Camp O.O. Denny Project File, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 8/11)
  - Camp O.O. Denny Designer Consultant Selection, 1981 (Box-folder 8/12)